<resources>
    <string name="faq_q_install_error">Why doesn’t the mod install or shows an import error?</string>
    <string name="faq_a_install_error">
• Make sure the mod version matches your Minecraft version.\n
• Supported versions are listed at the bottom of the mod page.\n
• Make sure you have enough free storage.\n
• Try restarting Minecraft and the app.
    </string>

    <string name="faq_q_not_visible">Why is the mod not showing in the game?</string>
    <string name="faq_a_not_visible">
• Open world settings and enable the mod manually.\n
• Make sure Experimental Features are enabled.\n
• Try creating a new world with this mod.
    </string>

    <string name="faq_q_no_internet">The app says there is no internet, but I have connection</string>
    <string name="faq_a_no_internet">
If you have internet but the app still shows an error, we are probably already aware of the issue.
There may be technical work on the server.
Please try again later.
    </string>

    <string name="faq_q_file_corrupted">Why does it say the file is corrupted?</string>
    <string name="faq_a_file_corrupted">
• The download may have been interrupted.\n
• Delete the mod and download it again.\n
• Check your internet connection.
    </string>

    <string name="faq_q_install_mod">How to install a mod?</string>
    <string name="faq_a_install_mod">
• Open the mod page.\n
• Click on the file.\n
• Tap Download.\n
• Wait until download finishes.\n
• Tap Install.\n
• Open the mod in Minecraft.
    </string>

    <string name="faq_q_install_texture">How to install a texture pack or skin?</string>
    <string name="faq_a_install_texture">
The process is the same as for mods.
After installation, enable it in Minecraft settings.
    </string>

    <string name="faq_q_need_internet">Do I need internet to use the app?</string>
    <string name="faq_a_need_internet">
Internet is required to download mods.
Installed mods work offline.
    </string>

    <string name="faq_q_new_mods">Will there be new mods?</string>
    <string name="faq_a_new_mods">Yes. We regularly add new mods and updates.</string>

    <string name="faq_q_not_working">Where to report if something doesn’t work?</string>
    <string name="faq_a_not_working">
On the mod screen, tap the “Not working” button.
Describe the problem in detail and we will try to help as soon as possible.
    </string>

    <string name="faq_q_share_mod">I have my own mod. How can I share it?</string>
    <string name="faq_a_share_mod">
You can suggest your mod directly in the app.
Tap the button below to open the submission screen.
    </string>

    <string name="faq_btn_submit_mod">Submit a mod</string>

    <string name="faq_q_multiplayer">Can I play with mods in multiplayer?</string>
    <string name="faq_a_multiplayer">
It depends on the server.
Usually the server must support the same mod.
    </string>

    <string name="faq_q_safe">Are mods safe?</string>
    <string name="faq_a_safe">
Yes. All mods are checked.
We do not publish viruses or malicious files.
    </string>

    <string name="faq_q_lag">Why does the mod lag?</string>
    <string name="faq_a_lag">
• Some mods are heavy for the device.\n
• Close other apps.\n
• Try lowering graphics settings in Minecraft.
    </string>

    <string name="faq_q_ads">Why does the app contain ads?</string>
    <string name="faq_a_ads">
Ads help us support and develop the app and keep mods updated.
We tried to make ads as unobtrusive as possible.
    </string>

</resources>
